[{"id": "5867fd5ade129f03113398d6", "question": "Where did Fonzie, Richie, Potsie and Ralph go to drink sodas and play the jukebox?", "answer": "Arnold's Drive-In", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5867fd5cde129f031133bb54", "question": "On what mountain does Moses speak to God through the burning bush and received the Ten Commandments?", "answer": "Mt. Sinai", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5867fd5bde129f031133ab13", "question": "Hobart is the capital of which Australian state?", "answer": "Tasmania", "category": "geography"}, {"id": "5b7ffb3b3a3a814d89068c63", "question": "Who is considered the Father of English literature?", "answer": "Geoffrey Chaucer", "category": "arts"}, {"id": "5867fd5ade129f031133978e", "question": "What is the name of the coolest girl gang in the movie \"Grease\"?", "answer": "The Pink Ladies", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5867fd5dde129f031133bfa8", "question": "Where do fallen Norse warriors go?", "answer": "Valhalla", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5867fd5dde129f031133c14a", "question": "Sophophobia is the fear of what?", "answer": "Learning", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5e8a8aaa404ad935a7e1a643", "question": "Which BTS member said their favorite hair color was red?", "answer": "V (Kim Tae-hyung)", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5867fd5bde129f031133a535", "question": "What is the largest lake found completely within the United States?", "answer": "Lake Michigan", "category": "geography"}, {"id": "5867fd5cde129f031133b26b", "question": "What country's Meiji Restoration began in 1866?", "answer": "Japan", "category": "history"}, {"id": "5867fd5cde129f031133b44d", "question": "What world leader was assassinated in Cairo on October 6, 1981?", "answer": "Anwar Sadat", "category": "history"}, {"id": "592eb0f6f83302ff91e464a2", "question": "What company makes the Vince Lombardi Trophy?", "answer": "Tiffany & Co.", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5867fd59de129f0311339490", "question": "Anthony Hopkins played a ventriloquist in which 1978 movie?", "answer": "Magic", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5867fd5ede129f031133ca64", "question": "What type of creature is an Orb Weaver?", "answer": "Spider", "category": "science"}, {"id": "5867fd5bde129f031133a8a9", "question": "What US state's National Guard still calls itself \"the Green Mountain Boys\"?", "answer": "Vermont", "category": "geography"}, {"id": "5fe6a65620565ad31a57c7d7", "question": "What was the name of the U.S ship on which the five Sullivan brothers died after it was torpedoed by the Japanese  during WWII?", "answer": "USS Juneau CL-52", "category": "history"}, {"id": "5867fd5ade129f0311339df1", "question": "What screen duo first appeared in the supporting cast of 1949's \"The Egg and I\"?", "answer": "Ma and Pa Kettle", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5867fd5cde129f031133af62", "question": "What was Typhoid Mary's job?", "answer": "Cook", "category": "history"}, {"id": "58d077e0870e6f05ba600868", "question": "Who directed the 1995 film \"Boys on the Side\"?", "answer": "Herbert Ross", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "59067f4eff9c0647b50a8082", "question": "In October of 2016, just 2 months after its initial release, what product did Samsung stop manufacturing and selling?", "answer": "Galaxy Note 7", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5fe8f79c01dd7bf43be5e837", "question": "\"Old Bill\" is a nickname or slang for whom?", "answer": "Police officers or law enforcement in the United Kingdom", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5fe7362aeec85e375820b25a", "question": "Who was the first Chairman of the US Joint Chiefs of Staff?", "answer": "General Omar Bradley", "category": "history"}, {"id": "5867fd5ade129f031133955c", "question": "What actor played \"Shoeless Joe\" Jackson in the movie \"Field of Dreams\"?", "answer": "Ray Liotta", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5867fd5bde129f031133a320", "question": "In which 2003 film did Hugh Grant play the British Prime Minister?", "answer": "Love Actually", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5867fd5dde129f031133c49b", "question": "Bubble wrap was invented accidentally by researchers who were trying to develop a new type of what?", "answer": "A 3-dimensional wallpaper", "category": "science"}, {"id": "5867fd5dde129f031133c3b1", "question": "What describes the amount of light allowed to pass through a camera lens?", "answer": "Aperture", "category": "science"}, {"id": "5ff7c3a82b316f4693fb67a9", "question": "Maxwell House coffee is named after what?", "answer": "Its first major customer, the now-defunct Maxwell House Hotel of Nashville, Tennessee.", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5867fd59de129f031133918c", "question": "Which witch is flattened by a house in \"The Wizard of Oz\"?", "answer": "The Wicked Witch of the East", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5fec8860ec223966ae8f881f", "question": "In what year was Michael Jackson featured as the halftime entertainment during the Super Bowl?", "answer": "1993 (Super Bowl XXVII)", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5867fd5ade129f0311339ef8", "question": "What's Mick Jagger's favorite soda, according to \"You Can't Always Get What You Want\"?", "answer": "Cherry red", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5867fd5cde129f031133b692", "question": "Klaxon horns were used on what type of vehicle during World War II?", "answer": "Submarines", "category": "general"}, {"id": "59db787d0ab2c8f322317ff3", "question": "What is the capital of Nova Scotia?", "answer": "Halifax", "category": "geography"}, {"id": "5867fd5cde129f031133b21c", "question": "What city was Wild Bill Hickok killed in?", "answer": "Deadwood", "category": "history"}, {"id": "5ff7c36c2b316f4693fb67a8", "question": "At which famous venue is a giant Christmas tree displayed each year in New York City?", "answer": "Rockefeller Center", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5fe12e01e39efa6330e0fed1", "question": "Where is the most expensive hotel suite in the U.S.?", "answer": "Las Vegas", "category": "geography"}, {"id": "5867fd5bde129f031133a30e", "question": "Which character did Evan Handler play on the TV show \"Californication\"?", "answer": "Charlie Runkle", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5867fd5dde129f031133c5d5", "question": "How many yards are there in a chain?", "answer": "22", "category": "science"}, {"id": "5867fd59de129f0311338a3e", "question": "What does pink kryptonite do to Superman?", "answer": "It turns him temporarily gay", "category": "arts"}, {"id": "5867fd59de129f0311338a0c", "question": "What is the name of the gypsy girl who Quasimodo fell in love with?", "answer": "Esmeralda", "category": "arts"}, {"id": "5ff0b1f4e662d71a53650fd6", "question": "Who created the famous sculpture \"The Thinker\"?", "answer": "Auguste Rodin", "category": "arts"}, {"id": "5fe9f0a9ff048f679a45aaa2", "question": "Selenophobia is the fear of what?", "answer": "The Moon", "category": "science"}, {"id": "5867fd5cde129f031133b863", "question": "What is the highest possible bowling score in a game with no strikes?", "answer": "190", "category": "general"}, {"id": "60121ae563c99d48cd169b09", "question": "An \"octothorpe\" refers to which popular social media symbol?", "answer": "Hashtag -- It is also called the \"pound sign\".", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5867fd59de129f0311339303", "question": "In the 2004 movie \"Anchorman: The Legend of Ron Burgundy\", what musical instrument does Ron play?", "answer": "The jazz flute", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5867fd59de129f0311338bb4", "question": "Which famous number was dreaded by people in Orwell\u2019s 1984?", "answer": "101", "category": "arts"}, {"id": "5fef5b7f6ce05a3942286e16", "question": "Where are the doldrums?", "answer": "Near the equator", "category": "geography"}, {"id": "5c77cdd024f0f7a362efd543", "question": "Who was the captain of the Bonhomme Richard in the 18th Century??", "answer": "John Paul Jones", "category": "history"}, {"id": "6018bbedd96d05b23b281651", "question": "The Peloponnesian War was fought between Athens and which other ancient Greek state?", "answer": "Sparta", "category": "history"}, {"id": "601737b944491cbd7c5a178d", "question": "What military leader is believed to have said, \"I can run wild for six months\u00a0... after that, I have no expectation of success\".", "answer": "Japanese Admiral\u00a0Isoroku Yamamoto -- He said this while predicting the future outcome of naval war against the U.S.", "category": "history"}, {"id": "5867fd5dde129f031133c6c5", "question": "What are the three main sections of an insect's body?", "answer": "The head, the abdomen and the thorax", "category": "science"}, {"id": "5f95b02755722f97b22684db", "question": "What does Dumbledore give to Ron in his will?", "answer": "Deluminator", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5867fd5bde129f031133a49b", "question": "In what country was the concentration camp \"Treblinka\" located?", "answer": "Poland", "category": "geography"}, {"id": "5867fd5dde129f031133c56f", "question": "Which Australian animal has unique fingerprints?", "answer": "Koala", "category": "science"}, {"id": "5867fd5bde129f031133a67e", "question": "Which US state is home to Wind Cave?", "answer": "South Dakota", "category": "geography"}, {"id": "5867fd59de129f0311338d9e", "question": "What author created the character of Tom Swift?", "answer": "Victor Appleton", "category": "arts"}, {"id": "5867fd5dde129f031133bced", "question": "Who chose her new name in 1953 to honor a Danish surgeon named Christian Hamburger?", "answer": "Christine Jorgensen", "category": "general"}, {"id": "6008de2df4f3bc4a292f8628", "question": "Who stated, \"Injustice anywhere is a threat to justice everywhere\".", "answer": "Dr. Martin Luther King, Jr. (He wrote it in his famous open letter known as \"Letter from Birmingham Jail\".)", "category": "history"}, {"id": "6015e43bfe83fe1f2a824baf", "question": "After the Battle of Kursk, the Germans did what?", "answer": "Began a lengthy retreat back to Germany.", "category": "history"}, {"id": "5867fd5ade129f03113398c8", "question": "What instrument was Jelly Roll Morton best known for playing?", "answer": "Piano", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5867fd5bde129f031133a464", "question": "Mount Rushmore is located near which town in South Dakota?", "answer": "Keystone", "category": "geography"}, {"id": "59ded085ea2747c8aff16d29", "question": "Ireland's River Shannon drains which basin?", "answer": "Shannon River Basin", "category": "geography"}, {"id": "5867fd5ede129f031133c9ca", "question": "Which Apollo mission carried Neil Armstrong and his team to the Moon?\u00a0", "answer": "Apollo 11", "category": "science"}, {"id": "5867fd5cde129f031133b091", "question": "What was the middle name of US Civil War Union General William T. Sherman?", "answer": "Tecumseh", "category": "history"}, {"id": "5867fd5ade129f0311339d64", "question": "Who played the role of TV's B. J. McKay?", "answer": "Greg Evigan", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5fea459bff048f679a45ab96", "question": "In which organ is vitamin A primarily stored?", "answer": "Liver", "category": "science"}, {"id": "5fe6a6b720565ad31a57c7dd", "question": "The aircraft carrier USS Lexington was lost in which World War II battle?", "answer": "The Battle of the Coral Sea", "category": "history"}, {"id": "5867fd5dde129f031133bd50", "question": "The Fields Medal is an award given in what field?", "answer": "Mathematics", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5867fd5bde129f031133a558", "question": "What is the capital of Washington?", "answer": "Olympia", "category": "geography"}, {"id": "5fffa78373838c5c8a417f39", "question": "What kind of animal is a bustard?", "answer": "Bird", "category": "science"}, {"id": "5867fd5ade129f0311339998", "question": "\"Citizens on Patrol\" and \"Mission to Moscow\" are subtitles of sequels to what 1980\u2019s series of movies?", "answer": "Police Academy", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5867fd5dde129f031133c3b3", "question": "What occurs when the Sun and the Moon are in conjunction as viewed from Earth?", "answer": "A solar eclipse", "category": "science"}, {"id": "5867fd5bde129f031133a9cc", "question": "In which modern day country would you find the region known as Transylvania?", "answer": "Romania", "category": "geography"}, {"id": "5867fd5ede129f031133c902", "question": "What is the fear of nudity known as?", "answer": "Gymnophobia or Nudophobia", "category": "science"}, {"id": "5867fd5bde129f031133a924", "question": "In what country is Magyar spoken?", "answer": "Hungary", "category": "geography"}, {"id": "5867fd5bde129f031133a9cf", "question": "What is the capital of the US state New Jersey?", "answer": "Trenton", "category": "geography"}, {"id": "5fefbe696ce05a3942286eef", "question": "Who recorded the song, \"I Heard a Rumour\"?", "answer": "Bananarama", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5867fd59de129f0311338e16", "question": "What cartoonist of \"Maus\" also created \"Topps Garbage Pail Kids\"?", "answer": "Art Spiegelman", "category": "arts"}, {"id": "6017371f44491cbd7c5a1784", "question": "Which ancient civilization has magical creatures known as Jinn?", "answer": "Persian - Jinn (sometimes spelled \"djinn\") are mythological creatures of fire and air that inspired most modern-day genie stories.", "category": "history"}, {"id": "5bc1d99ed702eaa27a66982a", "question": "Which Swedish musician sang the song \"Save Tonight\"?", "answer": "Eagle-Eye Cherry", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5867fd5ade129f0311339bb4", "question": "What comic played the lead in the 2009 movie \"Paul Blart: Mall Cop\"?", "answer": "Kevin James", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5867fd59de129f031133940a", "question": "What was the nickname given to the mechanical sharks created for the movie \"Jaws\"?", "answer": "Bruce", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5867fd5ade129f031133a14b", "question": "Who is the youngest member of the band Boyzone?", "answer": "Ronan Keating", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5b7abafb6490a8cc1a6e5292", "question": "In Roman numerals, what number does \"D\" represent?", "answer": "500", "category": "science"}, {"id": "5867fd5bde129f031133a259", "question": "What year did Alfred Hitchcock die?", "answer": "1980", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "60136eff1381754895396372", "question": "In the film \"The Green Mile\", what was the brand of Mr. Jingles cigar box?", "answer": "Marsh Wheeling -- It is the oldest cigar manufacturer in the U.S.", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5867fd5ade129f031133958a", "question": "What male actor plays the lead role in the 2005 movie \"The Island\"?", "answer": "Ewen McGregor", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5fe90a4f01dd7bf43be5e89a", "question": "What is the name for excessive bodily hair growth in women?", "answer": "Hursutism", "category": "science"}, {"id": "5fefa9596ce05a3942286ee0", "question": "What was the name of the Lone Ranger\u2019s horse?", "answer": "Silver", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5fea4466ff048f679a45ab8d", "question": "What snake will roll over and fake a gruesome death to confuse its attacker?", "answer": "Hog-nosed snake", "category": "science"}, {"id": "5867fd5cde129f031133afd2", "question": "What US city was destroyed by an earthquake in 1906?", "answer": "San Francisco", "category": "history"}, {"id": "5867fd5ade129f031133974d", "question": "What is Alecia Moore better known as?", "answer": "P!NK", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5867fd5dde129f031133c6c7", "question": "Hurricane season in the North Atlantic officially begins on the first day of what month?", "answer": "June", "category": "science"}, {"id": "5867fd59de129f0311339090", "question": "In Greek mythology, who was the god of the underworld?", "answer": "Hades", "category": "arts"}, {"id": "5867fd5bde129f031133a4cd", "question": "What seaport's name is Spanish for \"white house\"?", "answer": "Casablanca", "category": "geography"}, {"id": "601b4c8e49076251badbead7", "question": "What was the name of the space capsule that carried the first woman in space?", "answer": "Vostok 6 -- It carried Soviet cosmonaut Valentina Tereshkova in space on 1963.", "category": "history"}, {"id": "5867fd58de129f03113388e3", "question": "Who is the author of the \"Bourne Trilogy\" novel series?", "answer": "Robert Ludlum", "category": "arts"}, {"id": "5ff66c9752a821ff76ae8b13", "question": "Prior to 1954, Veterans Day was known as what in the US?", "answer": "Armistice Day", "category": "history"}, {"id": "59a551be3e1c6f9840ba318f", "question": "Corfu is part of which country?", "answer": "Greece", "category": "geography"}, {"id": "5867fd5cde129f031133af81", "question": "What was Paul Revere's profession?", "answer": "Silversmith", "category": "history"}, {"id": "5867fd5bde129f031133a858", "question": "Which river does the Brooklyn Bridge cross?", "answer": "East River", "category": "geography"}, {"id": "5867fd5dde129f031133c6ff", "question": "What famous chemist died in 1934 from a blood disease contracted by the effects of radiation exposure?", "answer": "Marie Curie", "category": "science"}, {"id": "5867fd5dde129f031133c3a9", "question": "What element is given the symbol \"I\"?", "answer": "Iodine", "category": "science"}, {"id": "5fe4dcf306d333868d34d6fd", "question": "Who won four gold medals in the 1936 Olympics, infuriating Adolf Hitler?", "answer": "Jessie Owens", "category": "history"}, {"id": "5867fd5dde129f031133bb70", "question": "Who led the NFL in rushing yards four out of five years from 1972 to 1976?", "answer": "O.J. Simpson", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5867fd59de129f0311338d33", "question": "What 1813 novel was turned into a movie starring Keira Knightly in 2005?", "answer": "Pride and Prejudice", "category": "arts"}, {"id": "5867fd59de129f031133906e", "question": "Which of the Bront&#279; siblings lived the longest?", "answer": "Charlotte", "category": "arts"}, {"id": "5867fd5ade129f03113395b1", "question": "In \"Bart vs. Australia,\" Homer threatened the members of Parliament with what?", "answer": "A big boot", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5867fd5ade129f0311339f49", "question": "Both of TV's \"Gilmore Girls\" have what first name?", "answer": "Lorelei", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "59ae92a7574a5ce6b56b8230", "question": "Who wrote the play \"The Rose Tattoo\"?", "answer": "Tennessee Williams", "category": "arts"}, {"id": "5867fd5cde129f031133b1f2", "question": "What was the last country in the Americas to abolish slavery, in 1888?", "answer": "Brazil", "category": "history"}, {"id": "5867fd5bde129f031133a373", "question": "What is the capital of Germany?", "answer": "Berlin", "category": "geography"}, {"id": "5956425b803c1f1ebcc4a02c", "question": "Tim McGraw and Faith Hill won the Academy of Country Music\u2019s very first Vocal Event trophy in 1997 for what song?", "answer": "\"It\u2019s Your Love\"", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "601b4b6649076251badbeac4", "question": "Maya Angelou spoke at the inauguration of which U.S. President?", "answer": "Maya Angelou recited her poem \"On the Pulse of Morning,\" at President Bill Clinton's first inauguration in 1993.", "category": "history"}, {"id": "5867fd5ade129f03113396ca", "question": "The TV show \"Frasier\" ran for how many seasons?", "answer": "11", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "6012150063c99d48cd169ae5", "question": "Einstein won the 1921 Nobel Prize for Physics for explaining what?", "answer": "Photoelectric effect -- However, that did not stop him from giving a lecture\u00a0on relativity in his acceptance speech.", "category": "history"}, {"id": "5fe6a8ab20565ad31a57c7f9", "question": "What was on the first-ever 12-inch record?", "answer": "Beethoven's Fifth Symphony", "category": "history"}, {"id": "590721263745b36be73039f5", "question": "Who played the role of Kris Kringle in the 1947 film \"Miracle on 34th Street\"?", "answer": "Edmund Gwenn", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5fefa9516ce05a3942286edf", "question": "What TV show inspired the F-16 combat plane nickname \"Viper\"?", "answer": "\"Battlestar Galactica\"", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5867fd5bde129f031133ab9a", "question": "The port of Piraeus serves which European capital?", "answer": "Athens", "category": "geography"}, {"id": "5867fd5ade129f031133996a", "question": "In the TV show \"The Simpsons\", who is Bart's fourth grade teacher?", "answer": "Edna Krabappel", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5867fd5dde129f031133be9c", "question": "Who washes his hands in Matthew 27:24?", "answer": "Pontius Pilate", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5867fd5ade129f0311339a0d", "question": "What was the title of the Kirstie Alley TV show in which her character ran a lingerie company?", "answer": "Veronica's Closet", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5867fd5bde129f031133aacb", "question": "Topeka is the capital of which US state?", "answer": "Kansas", "category": "geography"}, {"id": "590722e33745b36be7303a03", "question": "What popular Christmas song did Eartha Kitt record in 1953?", "answer": "Santa Baby", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5867fd5dde129f031133c03d", "question": "Sociophobia is the fear of what?", "answer": "Society and social situations", "category": "general"}, {"id": "6014c993fbde8045e48466ef", "question": "What is a group of jelly fish called?", "answer": "A smack", "category": "science"}, {"id": "5867fd5bde129f031133ab68", "question": "In what Australian state would you find the major port town Fremantle?", "answer": "Western Australia", "category": "geography"}, {"id": "5867fd5bde129f031133a5b5", "question": "The Golden Gate Bridge is located in what city?", "answer": "San Francisco", "category": "geography"}, {"id": "5867fd5dde129f031133c0ed", "question": "What is the fear of mice known as?", "answer": "Musophobia", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5867fd59de129f0311338d0d", "question": "Uriah Heep was a character in what Charles Dickens novel?", "answer": "David Copperfield", "category": "arts"}, {"id": "5e147a756ca6dac04a20ca4f", "question": "When did Thomas Jefferson purchase the territory of Louisiana?", "answer": "1803", "category": "geography"}, {"id": "5fef64996ce05a3942286e67", "question": "What is the smallest theater on Broadway?", "answer": "The Helen Hayes Theatre", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5fe8b1f201dd7bf43be5e797", "question": "What does it mean to \"86\" something?", "answer": "Get rid of it", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5fd2d0ad2596a59cbdfbd37f", "question": "Who said, \"If a man is proud of his wealth, he should not be praised until it is known how he employs it\"?", "answer": "Socrates", "category": "history"}, {"id": "5f178122b8195c09b948d5c1", "question": "Who was the emperor of Ethiopia from 1930 to 1974?", "answer": "Haile Selassie", "category": "history"}, {"id": "5ad7e776b24f84e0b9f9ffb9", "question": "Where is the Pettit National Ice Center located?", "answer": "Milwaukee, Wisconsin", "category": "geography"}, {"id": "5867fd5dde129f031133c107", "question": "What fruit is used in making \"Creme de Cassis\"?", "answer": "Blackcurrants\u00a0", "category": "general"}, {"id": "58d076f8870e6f05ba600860", "question": "In Shakespeare's \"The Taming of the Shrew\", who is the shrew's father?", "answer": "Baptista Minola", "category": "arts"}, {"id": "5ad9e1b6e748bb36357acdf6", "question": "Who is the singer behind the albums \"1989\" and \"Reputation\"?", "answer": "Taylor Swift", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5867fd59de129f0311338e53", "question": "What literary work inspired Green Day's \"Who Wrote Holden Caufield\" song?", "answer": "The Catcher in the Rye", "category": "arts"}, {"id": "58bb34e9e368446ca7bd684c", "question": "What widely consumed drug acts as a natural defence to protect the seeds of the coffee plant?", "answer": "Caffeine", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5fea353bff048f679a45aaff", "question": "Which planet is known as the Evening Star?", "answer": "Venus", "category": "science"}, {"id": "5867fd59de129f03113393a2", "question": "Who plays Jullia Robert's best friend in the movie \"My Best Friend's Wedding\"?", "answer": "Dermot Mulroney", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5867fd5ade129f031133962c", "question": "In what movie does Cary Grant play a ghost?", "answer": "Topper", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5fea77a2ff048f679a45abcb", "question": "What is another name for the vitamin B3?", "answer": "Niacin", "category": "science"}, {"id": "59cdb1ef65ff7d326b622a6e", "question": "Animals and plants which produce light are said to be what?", "answer": "Bioluminescent", "category": "science"}, {"id": "5867fd5dde129f031133c014", "question": "Which car company was founded by Sir William Lyons in 1922?", "answer": "Jaguar", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5fd96c3823c87fd04dd15e21", "question": "What Jelly Belly flavor was created for Ronald Reagan's inauguration?", "answer": "Blueberry", "category": "history"}, {"id": "5b7ff9c53a3a814d89068c57", "question": "What unit of measurement is one tenth of a nautical mile?", "answer": "A Cable", "category": "science"}, {"id": "59029db7cad1ec93f27df751", "question": "What popular French apple brandy is made by distilling cider made from selected apples?", "answer": "Calvados", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5867fd5ade129f031133a153", "question": "Who is Placebo's lead singer?", "answer": "Brian Molko", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5fe69b6a20565ad31a57c75e", "question": "What was the last major battle in World War II?", "answer": "Battle of Okinawa", "category": "history"}, {"id": "5867fd59de129f0311338ac5", "question": "What quality does a \"rhopalic\" sentence have?", "answer": "Each word has one more letter or syllable than the previous word", "category": "arts"}, {"id": "5867fd5dde129f031133c5d8", "question": "How many fluid ounces in a gill?", "answer": "5", "category": "science"}, {"id": "5867fd5bde129f031133ac4e", "question": "What was the code name for the development of the A-bomb?", "answer": "The Manhattan Project", "category": "history"}, {"id": "5fef5bfb6ce05a3942286e1c", "question": "Despite being a film about an American World War II hero, who was the only American who had a role in the film \"Hacksaw Ridge\"?", "answer": "Vince Vaughn", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5867fd59de129f031133916c", "question": "Who plays the role of Laura Silverman on the TV show \"The Sarah Silverman Program\"?", "answer": "Laura Silverman", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5867fd59de129f03113393ee", "question": "According to the 1973 movie, soylent green is what?", "answer": "People", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5867fd5ede129f031133c8d7", "question": "How many diagonals does a triangle have?", "answer": "None", "category": "science"}, {"id": "5867fd5bde129f031133a356", "question": "Where is Pennsylvania Station?", "answer": "New York City", "category": "geography"}, {"id": "5867fd5cde129f031133ba35", "question": "What brand of whiskey is made in Lynchburg, Tennessee?", "answer": "Jack Daniels", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5867fd5ade129f03113397fe", "question": "On the cover of the \"Let It Be\" album, which Beatle had the least amount of facial hair?", "answer": "John Lennon", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "6010ca8b0775fa611bce67fa", "question": "For what category is the Charlemagne Prize awarded?", "answer": "Work toward European unification -- Awarded to projects run by persons aged 16 to 30 that promote the idea of a unified Europe.", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5867fd5dde129f031133c7ef", "question": "What vegetable secretes a psychotropic fluid called \"lactucarium\"?", "answer": "Lettuce", "category": "science"}, {"id": "5867fd5cde129f031133b8a3", "question": "In which decade were the first Winter Olympic Games held?", "answer": "1920s", "category": "general"}, {"id": "60077fd2bd51d85e222ab640", "question": "What was the official diagnosis when van Gogh was hospitalized in 1888?", "answer": "When Van Gogh was hospitalized on Christmas Eve 1888 in Ales, his official diagnosis was \"acute mania with generalised delirium\".", "category": "arts"}, {"id": "5867fd5ade129f0311339de2", "question": "What \"Desperate Housewives\" creator broke into TV as a personal assistant to actress Dixie Carter?", "answer": "Marc Cherry", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5867fd59de129f0311339387", "question": "Who was the Castle Rock DJ in the movie \"Stand By Me\"?", "answer": "Bob Cormier", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5867fd5cde129f031133b84b", "question": "The Ryder Cup is awarded in what sport?", "answer": "Golf", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5fd660a8a5bfecdd737e0836", "question": "What did \"RMS\" in RMS Titanic stand for?", "answer": "Royal Mail Ship", "category": "history"}, {"id": "5867fd5ade129f0311339f78", "question": "What was Buddy Holly's backing band?", "answer": "The Crickets", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5fd2d0442596a59cbdfbd379", "question": "Who said, \"When I do good, I feel good. When I do bad, I feel bad. That's my religion\"?", "answer": "Abraham Lincoln", "category": "history"}, {"id": "5867fd5cde129f031133b809", "question": "Who are the Mario Brothers usually trying to save?", "answer": "Princess Peach", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5867fd59de129f0311338a26", "question": "Whose \"Small House\" is the subject of the play acted out during \"The King and I\"?", "answer": "Uncle Thomas'", "category": "arts"}, {"id": "5867fd5cde129f031133afa8", "question": "At which famous American battle was General Custer defeated by Sitting Bull?", "answer": "Little Bighorn", "category": "history"}, {"id": "5867fd5dde129f031133c3d7", "question": "Emollients are more commonly referred to as what?", "answer": "Moisturizers", "category": "science"}, {"id": "5867fd5bde129f031133abf4", "question": "What state capital city lies on the River Torrens?", "answer": "Adelaide", "category": "geography"}, {"id": "58dba71e874c93a3298b2161", "question": "What is Ace Frehley\u2019s persona name in the band KISS?", "answer": "Spaceman or Space Ace", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "58b8ccac94b094db915830a1", "question": "How many Oscars have been awarded from inception through the 88th Academy Awards?", "answer": "3,048", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "6015e8cdfe83fe1f2a824bdf", "question": "Which rebellious leader of the Catuvellauni tribe was caught and taken to Rome in AD 50, then pardoned by Emperor Claudius?", "answer": "Caractacus", "category": "history"}, {"id": "5867fd59de129f0311338af4", "question": "The novel \"Life of Pi\" takes place in which ocean?", "answer": "The Pacific Ocean", "category": "arts"}, {"id": "5867fd5bde129f031133a666", "question": "What US city is home to the International UFO Museum and Research Center?", "answer": "Roswell", "category": "geography"}, {"id": "5867fd5cde129f031133b65a", "question": "Hall of Fame running back Jim Brown played his entire pro career for which NFL team?", "answer": "Cleveland Browns", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5c90cee852800b05cac20f06", "question": "What is the only MLB team that has never had a pitcher throw a no-hitter as of 2018?", "answer": "San Diego Padres", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5a9e95f77ccba3ffe45786e6", "question": "Whose autobiography was entitled \"The Sport of Queens\"?", "answer": "Dick Francis'", "category": "arts"}, {"id": "5867fd5ade129f0311339f45", "question": "What sheriff's alter ego was the masked \"El Kabong\"?", "answer": "Quick Draw McGraw's", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5867fd5dde129f031133c6c8", "question": "Which eye color is normally dominant in humans?", "answer": "Brown", "category": "science"}, {"id": "5867fd5dde129f031133be6b", "question": "What is Dodger Stadium also known as?", "answer": "Chavez Ravine", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5867fd5cde129f031133b0ba", "question": "In what town was FDR's \"Little White House\" located?", "answer": "Warm Springs, Georgia", "category": "history"}, {"id": "5c88e64c22f44c2d77a29c40", "question": "What war hero, later the 7th American President, led the Americans to victory in the Battle of New Orleans?", "answer": "Andrew Jackson", "category": "history"}, {"id": "59029f1ccad1ec93f27df75b", "question": "At what popular Seattle market did Starbucks open its first store in 1971?", "answer": "Pike Place", "category": "history"}, {"id": "5909d2f6bb53d1af6588650e", "question": "Who played the lead role in the 1983 film \"Merry Christmas, Mr. Lawrence\"?", "answer": "David Bowie", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5ffa57fbc73aa70ea0b70b37", "question": "Which U.S. state features the Italian phrase \"Fatti maschii, parole femine\" as its state motto?", "answer": "Maryland  (The motto translates as \u201cManly deeds, womanly words.\u201d\u00a0 The state uses\u00a0\"Strong deeds, gentle words\".)", "category": "geography"}, {"id": "594d06551a1c922dd1ac64aa", "question": "What nation has had its own scandals dubbed \"Muldergate\" and \"Inkathagate\"?", "answer": "South Africa", "category": "history"}, {"id": "5867fd5bde129f031133a473", "question": "In which ocean are the Seychelles?", "answer": "Indian", "category": "geography"}, {"id": "5867fd5ade129f0311339e9e", "question": "What movie did the villain Regina Giddens appear in?", "answer": "The Little Foxes", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5867fd5ade129f0311339e83", "question": "What future game show host had a Top Forty hit with 1968's \"Naturally Stoned\"?", "answer": "Chuck Woolery", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5867fd5cde129f031133af4f", "question": "During the 20th Century, in what year did the annexation of Austria by German take place?", "answer": "1938", "category": "history"}, {"id": "59ca3dd044f0f6af5b066640", "question": "Andorra la Vella is the capital of which European country?", "answer": "Andorra", "category": "geography"}, {"id": "5867fd5bde129f031133a9e2", "question": "In which Chinese city is the Terracotta Army?", "answer": "Xian", "category": "geography"}, {"id": "5867fd59de129f0311338e33", "question": "What children's classic first chapter is titled \"Down the Rabbit-Hole\"?", "answer": "Alice in Wonderland", "category": "arts"}, {"id": "5867fd5ade129f031133956d", "question": "Which cowboy musical artist first recorded the song, Here Comes Santa Claus?", "answer": "Gene Autry", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "59db75050ab2c8f322317fe3", "question": "On which coast would you find the smallest Canadian province?", "answer": "East coast", "category": "geography"}, {"id": "6010c9ef0775fa611bce67f0", "question": "What breed of dog was used to popularize the phrase \"Yo quiero Taco Bell\"?", "answer": "Chihuahua -- Gidget, the 8-pound female Chihuahua, was only Taco Bell\u2019s mascot for 3 years, but she made the most of her time.", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5867fd59de129f0311339054", "question": "What was the name of Sherlock Holmes' intelligent brother?", "answer": "Mycroft", "category": "arts"}, {"id": "5867fd5dde129f031133c769", "question": "What word describes the enlargement of bone or tissue at the joint between the big toe and the foot?", "answer": "Bunion", "category": "science"}, {"id": "5867fd5ade129f0311339b80", "question": "What 1991 movie featured the character Topper Harley?", "answer": "Hot Shots!", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5fdfbe8e003d27d341092bd0", "question": "Why are Amsterdam's buildings so narrow?", "answer": "A tax loophole", "category": "geography"}, {"id": "5867fd59de129f0311338ea7", "question": "In what comic strip would you find siblings Chip, Dot, Ditto and Trixie?", "answer": "Hi and Lois", "category": "arts"}, {"id": "5867fd59de129f0311338da1", "question": "What author created the character of Tom Hagen?", "answer": "Mario Puzo", "category": "arts"}, {"id": "5867fd5cde129f031133b3a2", "question": "Who was the first victim of the electric chair?", "answer": "William Francis Kemmler", "category": "history"}, {"id": "5867fd59de129f0311339222", "question": "As a child, what did Casper the Friendly Ghost die from?", "answer": "Pneumonia", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5867fd58de129f031133896d", "question": "What Jane Austen novel has a main character named Fanny Price?", "answer": "Mansfield Park", "category": "arts"}, {"id": "5867fd59de129f0311338c11", "question": "According to Exodus, what is the ninth plague of Egypt?", "answer": "Darkness", "category": "arts"}, {"id": "5867fd5ade129f0311339dfc", "question": "What \"Family Feud\" actor ended up committing suicide?", "answer": "Ray Combs", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5867fd5ade129f0311339606", "question": "Who was the fugitive in the 1993 movie by the same name?", "answer": "Dr. Richard Kimble", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5867fd5ade129f0311339f92", "question": "What actress earned an Oscar nomination for her first screen appearance in \"Alfie\"?", "answer": "Vivien Merchant", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5989a8abcb8751d53e7d75fd", "question": "Who won Super Bowl IV?", "answer": "Kansas City Chiefs", "category": "history"}, {"id": "5867fd5dde129f031133be0d", "question": "What are the two fruit juices in a cosmopolitan?", "answer": "Cranberry and lime", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5867fd5cde129f031133aecc", "question": "Where was South Africa's Freedom Charter signed?", "answer": "Kliptown", "category": "history"}, {"id": "5867fd5dde129f031133bedd", "question": "In the game of chess, which piece has the most freedom to move?", "answer": "The queen", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5989ad39cb8751d53e7d760e", "question": "An 1849 painting by Asher Durand, and a sculpture situated in Bailick Park in Midleton, Ireland,share what name?", "answer": "Kindred Spirits", "category": "arts"}, {"id": "58b370281c3f17ccc40c8e11", "question": "What is \"pub\" short for?", "answer": "Public House", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5867fd5cde129f031133b1a1", "question": "Which staircase in the Leaning Tower of Pisa has fewer steps?", "answer": "The north-facing one", "category": "history"}, {"id": "5867fd5cde129f031133b4a6", "question": "Which country were the 1932 Winter Olympic Games held in?", "answer": "United States", "category": "history"}, {"id": "5867fd5ade129f0311339d40", "question": "What two popular TV shows are based in the town of Hooterville?", "answer": "Green Acres and Petticoat Junction", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5ff25b0531a458464a93c475", "question": "Shito pepper is a commonly used condiment in which part of the world?", "answer": "West Africa", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5a4d98c308b8581f80b092b0", "question": "Approximately how much was the price of a single Bitcoin on January 1, 2017?", "answer": "$1,000 USD", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5867fd5dde129f031133bc7a", "question": "What word for a retired professional comes from the Latin for \"having earned a discharge\"?", "answer": "Emeritus", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5fe9058301dd7bf43be5e87d", "question": "What does \"In absentia lucis, Tenebrae vincunt\" translate into?", "answer": "In absence of light, darkness prevails", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5867fd5bde129f031133a75f", "question": "How many countries border Chile?", "answer": "3", "category": "geography"}, {"id": "5b358a735db0d66a186cb553", "question": "What is the birth name of actress Paula Prentiss?", "answer": "Paula Ragusa", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "59524686736d4be723796b70", "question": "Robert Llewellyn, Craig Charles, Danny John-Jules and Chris Barrie are known for acting in which British Sci-Fi comedy show?", "answer": "Red Dwarf", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5867fd5bde129f031133adb1", "question": "What event inspired Herbert Morrison's famous quote \"Oh, the humanity!\"?", "answer": "The Hindenburg disaster", "category": "history"}, {"id": "5867fd59de129f0311338d7d", "question": "Who was the real-life model for the character of Jack Stanton in the novel \"Primary Colors\"?", "answer": "Bill Clinton", "category": "arts"}, {"id": "5fe7beaa877e98cb97778962", "question": "What Hawaiian island is known as \"Bird Island\"?", "answer": "Nihoa", "category": "geography"}, {"id": "5867fd5cde129f031133b939", "question": "What is the usual age for a Jewish boy to celebrate his Bar Mitzvah?", "answer": "13", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5867fd5cde129f031133b7dc", "question": "What are the four railways in the standard version of Monopoly?", "answer": "The B&O, Pennsylvania, Reading, Short Line", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5867fd58de129f03113388ed", "question": "What Harry Potter character has the patronus of a hare/bunny?", "answer": "Luna Lovegood", "category": "arts"}, {"id": "59008e40cf842fa4c4ba96b0", "question": "During which war did the \"Battle of Jutland\" take place?", "answer": "World War I", "category": "history"}, {"id": "5867fd5cde129f031133ba66", "question": "What branch of the U.S. military features the Blue Angels precision flying squad?", "answer": "US Navy", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5867fd5dde129f031133c393", "question": "What tube connects the larynx to the lungs?", "answer": "The trachea", "category": "science"}, {"id": "594a63192ebb971c1417fb97", "question": "What year did the \"Turbot War\" fishing dispute end?", "answer": "1996", "category": "history"}, {"id": "58c89e24011619dd6d41548b", "question": "In season 16 of South Park, what chain store did Randy buy for $10,000?", "answer": "Blockbuster", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5867fd5bde129f031133a9a2", "question": "What nation is home to the ancient Grand Canal?", "answer": "China", "category": "geography"}, {"id": "5fea7cceff048f679a45abf9", "question": "What does the Ka\u0301rma\u0301n Line represent?", "answer": "The edge of space", "category": "science"}, {"id": "5867fd5bde129f031133a9f2", "question": "How many US states border an ocean?", "answer": "23", "category": "geography"}, {"id": "5867fd5cde129f031133b031", "question": "Who was the last US president of the 19th century?", "answer": "William McKinley", "category": "history"}, {"id": "5867fd5ade129f031133a138", "question": "Who sang the theme song to the film \"The Breakfast Club\"?", "answer": "Simple Minds", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5867fd59de129f0311338edb", "question": "What famous horse belonged to Don Quixote?", "answer": "Rocinante", "category": "arts"}, {"id": "5867fd5bde129f031133a837", "question": "The Liffey River runs through what European capital city?", "answer": "Dublin", "category": "geography"}, {"id": "5867fd5bde129f031133a2ae", "question": "Whose movie character's full name is Charles Lee Ray?", "answer": "Chucky", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5fec85d2ec223966ae8f880a", "question": "According to the timeline of the movie \"The Shawshank Redemption\", in what year did Andy make his daring escape?", "answer": "1966", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5867fd5bde129f031133a37a", "question": "What is the capital of Portugal?", "answer": "Lisbon", "category": "geography"}, {"id": "5867fd5ade129f0311339aad", "question": "What popular children\u2019s book did Forrest Gump keep in his briefcase?", "answer": "Curious George", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5867fd59de129f0311338cbb", "question": "Who wrote \"Breakfast at Tiffany's\"?", "answer": "Truman Capote", "category": "arts"}]